What happens to this city?
Either there is ash or smoke.
Why doesn't anyone say anything?
Why do they tolerate
this smoke quietly?
It's the limit to tolerance.
Let's douse cigarettes and cigars.
There is a ban on smoking
in public places.
You've to pay a ﬁne.
Don't smoke, don't let others smoke.
You've to pay dearly for smoking.
Everyone desires happiness.
But at what cost?
Smoking costs dearly.
Smoking is injurious
to your health"
"to your loves ones too.
You've to pay dearly for smoking.
"What is life? A delicate arrangement
of the ﬁve elements..."
"What is death? A disarray of these
elements" - Brij Narayan Chakbast
One moment
I've brought you a gift
Thank you
Are you okay?
Feels a bit weird, doesn't it?
Open the door!
What ﬁlth are you up to?
My clothes?
Open the dour!!!
WOW !
Turned this into a bazaar, eh?
Well done!
Move it!
Get his name
Your name!
- Piyush Agarwal
What do you do?
- Sir, I am a student
I am a student, sir!
Where are you from?
- Allahabad
Allahabad
ls this what they leach you?
Can't we agree on a settlement?
Show him a good "settlement"!
I will 'settle' things
with madam till then
Your name?
Name?!
Say it!
- Devi
Devi, you're life is now ruined
Piyush!
- Catch him!
Drag him out!
Let's work out that "settlement"
you asked for
No, sir!
I'm a college student, Sir.
It's my ﬁrst time here
Come out, you brat!
Open up!
Get me his wallet
Open the door!
This will get him
out in a minute!
Father's name: Ramdhari Agarwal
Emergency number: 9415257547
Come out now kiddo,
or your dad gets the call
Sir... I just want to use the toilet
You can shit in prison.
Your dad's phone is busy
Please don't call my dad!
I beg you!
We will call him again, shortly
Please let us go
Where are you from?
The local brothel?
Face the camera
No
- From Nepal?
You've got it wrong
Really? We've got it wrong?
What are you waiting for?
Break open the damn door!
Come out now!
Are you at a confessional?
Knock it down!
Sir!
_ Yes?
Sir, look what he's done!
What now?
Hey Pandey!
Call the ambulance
Hurry UP
Careful !
Get her dressed and
take her to the station
Home already, son?
Let me get you some water
It's okay, I'll get it myself
I'll get it
Mother, it's time to prepare the stove
Son, get holy ﬁre to ﬁre up the stove
Wake Sikandar up too,
his shift starts soon
Brother!
Brother...
Sikandar...
Mother sent me to wake you up
Wake up!
Ram, the name of God,
is eternal truth!
Dad, I'll light the stove
and be back
And Sikandar?
- He's up... on his way here
Mr. Motilal...
Come, have some sweets
I can't leave my shop unattended
Come on! Nobody's going
to steal anything
They've got sweets.
They're from the university, right?
We're doing an anthropology project
They want to know about our ghats,
enlighten them
You're our ghat scholar!
And you, our scholar on shady alleys!
The sleazy ones at night!
You're recording this?
Yes sir, one tends to miss
details while writing
History... Huh?
Earlier, the banks of Mother
Ganges were a vast forest
Cremation rituals began
in the Holy River
So, various kings set up ghats
Priests from all over
started settling here
Ghats were assigned...
according to state, caste...
and priests
Did you understand?
The ghat we're sitting on right now...
is under dispute
Like Kashmir
-Yes, like Kashmir
The Maharasthrians claim
it to be theirs...
as so do the Gujratis
What do we do with this brat?
Meet Jhonta. Ghat hero,
running for president...
but ask him to get me customers
and he runs like an athlete!
What happened?
- I was about to...
Bring me my phone!
Hurry up! Now!
The Scindia ghat, the one
right next to ours...
I'll look for customers, master!
Kids these days are so restless,
always on the run
And so is this wretched phone
Misery of modern times!
Hello?
Yes, speaking
Look at the ingenuity of
these kids
She changed into a
saree, all spruced up
They barely knew each
other...
and just look ham!
What for?
What did you tell us a while back?
Say it out loud
Enlighten your father
What was that phrase?
"Curbing curiosity!"
lfl tip off ajournalist...
it would make the front page
What is this?
A ﬁle of another department
on my desk?
What shit!!
Make the corrections and
get out of my face!
What is your name again?
Pathak
Vidhyadhar Pathak
I offer ritual services
at Nandeshwar ghat
I used to be a Sanskrit
professor at the university
Now I translate
- We'll call you in 3 days
Pay the bail here, and take
your daughter for now
Mr. Mishra,
what do you mean "for now"?
If anything happens to the boy...
it'll be a case of
abetment of suicide
Court, media, journalists,
the whole shebang!
No pleading!
Go pay the bail over there
We're from
the same community
Go pay the bail and
get out!
Centrifugal force turned into centripetal
and people hit a deadlock there...
so they started moving upwards
And this led to the birth of
Civil Engineering
Any question?
No, sir!
You can do this alone
- Come on, I need the support
Add some ﬂavoured corn in it
Some green chilies on the side
Roast it properW!
Like always
Of course, madam!
Exactly the way you want it
Pooja!
Happy Birthday to you!
Please?
Thank you
Did you like it?
So when is the birthday treat?
How will she explain
this to her folks?
As in?
How will she explain who
gave this huge gift?
I'm cool with any excuse
Oh really?
Give this to me
Here, take this back
No, I got this as a gift
Gifts are not supposed to be
returned. Come on now!
But what will she tell her folks?
Add more of these peanuts
Say something
- She can say you've gifted it to her
Like her folks are going
to believe that!
Enough, don't roast it more!
A dash of green sauce too
More of these chilli ﬂakes as well
Last time you put very
little garlic in it
Be generous this time
- Yes, madam
Have you ever heard of a girl gifting a
teddy bear to another girl?
Don't they?
Nor have I ever seen a girl
fuss over a 5 rupee snack!
We need to go
Take this teddy with you
No, thanks, we're in a hurry!
Let's go
Good morning, master!
I had an early bath today!
You haven't shown up for 3 days
Mind your own business
ls your father home?
He's gone to the ghat
Call him
The boy is dead
Did you offer some tea?
Have a seat
Sorry, I'm late
Well, the boy didn't survive
They're doing an autopsy and
we'll have the report soon
Here are the court papers
Please ﬁll them up
Wait...
what do we have to do
with the court?
It's a case of abetment of suicide
But the boy...
killed himself on your watch
I mean... because of
police initimidation
So now you are acting the Professor?
Here's the thing...
you can save your lecture to jerk off
your ghat customers
Okay?
You must have seen it on TV?
The R.K Puram sex scandal,
Jammu and Kashmir sex scandal
Your daughter is now part of
a big sex scandal!
Sir, please suggest a way out
How much do you earn?
Around 8 to 10 thousand rupees
She earns as well, right?
Yes... at a computer
coaching institute
I won't beat around the bush
Abetment...
media, court...
I can handle all of that
But you'll have to
make arrangements
3 lakh rupees.
I'm giving you 3 months
Sir, you've got us wrong
We're principled people
We can hardly manage 50,000 rupees!
From now on...
never ever...
ever... negotiate with me
Am I selling you a bloody
soap?!
I'm hereto save your honour
I have your daughter's sex
scandal video on my phone
One upload and the whole city
will get off on your daughter!
Arrange 1 lakh Rupees in two days
Don't just nod like a horse!
What will you do?
Arrange 1 lakh Rupees
in two days
And, after 2 months?
2 lakh Rupees
ls the math really that hard?
Where to Madam?
To the cremation ghat
- It's forbidden for women
Hit the skull hard, 5 times
Deepak, give him a hand
Piyush! My son!
Harder! Smash the skull
to release the soul!
How many more days
left in college?
Two more months, Dad
Then exams and placements!
\Nhat?
- I mean job placements
Don't you need to
pay something to get ajob?
Not anymore, Mother
The Railway and Electric companies...
hire on merit
Instead of supervising the ash cleaning,
you're feasting here?
What if the boys steal the
silver?
Uncle Shambhu is supervising it
Shambu is a pothead!
So? Am I not even
supposed to eat?
How much will the job pay?
They will let me know
after the interview
Great! Get out of this place
The sooner, the better
Otherwise, even your life will
end up torching bodies
Bread!
Look what I found,
I think it's silver!
Show me!
Throw it you fool. It's aluminium
Will you ever explain yourself?
I met him at the
coaching centre
I used to type out his thesis...
and we became friends
That's all?
Yes, I felt nice talking to him
Did you even think twice
before doing it?
Even once?
Did you?
Answer me!
What?
Cat got your tongue?
- I don't know
A boy just killed himself
A ransom of 3 lakhs on our heads
ljust broke my 1 lakh Rupees
ﬁxed deposit
You're one step away from jail...
and you say "l don't know"
I ﬁshed out 26 Rupees
Please, let me be part
of the competition
Are you actually asking me
to let you gamble?
It's not gambling!
It's sport and
I have become a pro at it
Why are you acting so smart?
Today I will play, no matter what
Why don't you shut up
and do some work!
Got screwed over by a bull or what?
Pooja looks so pretty with the teddy
Cute, isn't she?
Can you ask
for her friend's name?
How would I ask?
"My friend has a crush
on your poetry-reading friend...
give me her name
so he can ask her out?"
Ok, how about we send
her a written request?
Deepak is getting
emotional about her
Like they say...
"Shake the mango all night,
it'll only fall off the tree
when it's time is ripe"
What is that noise there?
Okay, listen...
do you remember what
she looks like?
Sure?
- Yes
Okay
This is her college group page.
She's got to be here
Won't you ﬁnd her
in Pooja's album?
Of course! She'll be in
Pooja's friend list
ls that her?
No
There... there... That's her!
Shaalu Gupta
Gupta family, eh?
Awesome, dude!
Now create your Facebook account
and let the ﬁreworks begin!
I mean send her
a friend request
Should we?
Yeah
Come one, come all, make big money!
Here's the super competition!
In half an hour, increase your gain!
10 rupees turns to 50! 50 turns to 200!
Now listen to the rules
These kids will dive in
and bring out coins!
Bet on the boy you think
will get the most coins
Great! We have your 20 Rupees on Lokua
Don't think twice!
Just place your bets!
20 Rupees on Netwa
The competition is about to begin!
1... 2...
Now let's see who
gets the most coins!
Lokua has 3 coins!
Netwa, hurry! Faster!
- Babua's got only one coin this time
Let's see who's winning...
Munna has 6 coins in one dive
Hold your breath folks
Please let me join in!
- No, just watch
Those who've bet on Netwa,
will get three times their money!
Hello?
Hello Devi?
Yes?
Where were you hiding
your phone all this while?
You think l am an idiot?
I know what dirty
business you've been up to
Bloody witch...
Move!
Hey!
What are you doing here?!
Who let you in?
I came hereto collect my stuff...
and if you make those ﬁlthy calls again,
I'll thrash the hell out of you!
He was our top student!
Weren't you ashamed to do it?
Whatever it was, we both
were equally involved
But he was the only one to die
Sikandar!
Thrust the leg into the
pyre, you idiot!
Sikandar!
Looks like the old man is drunk
Pour me another drink
‘King of the Dams‘!
One more for your health!
Do I look like a king to you?
Come on! There are only
two kings in Banaras!
One is Kashi Naresh and
the other is the Dom king
One on that side...
and one on this side
Look at that miserable Shambu
How rnany 'bonus days' in a year?
Hey! Shambu!
Yes, sir!
Once every 10 years
Sharnbhu gets a 'bonus day'
every 10 years!
Meaning?
That day...
he gets all the money
from every cremation here
Shambu's father...
got his 'bonus day' once in a year
Overjoyed by that,
he had ten children
The 'bonus day' got split
Since the father
had one day in a year...
Sharnbhu inherited
a tenth of the 'bonus day'
Now he has one every 10 years
\N'hen is your next 'bonus day', Sharnbu'?
Never again
I sold my rights to Lala
He gave me 1 Iakh Rupees for it
I'll live the rest of my life off alms
lfl sell rny 'bonus day'...
I'll get over 10 lakh Rupees.
Right, lala?
As if you are ever going
to sell it to me
Should we sell?
Asking your ignorant son?
He has nothing to do with
our cremation ghat!
He's nothing but an educated fool!
You're insulting my son?
I'll never sell rny 'bonus day' to you!
As if you'd ever think to do so!
Father, I need some money.
For the Durga Puja Carnival
There, in my shirt
May I take 300 Rupees?
Take as much as you want
You're the only one!
Are you going to the Durga puja
carnival tonight?
20 rupees
Put the watch in the hat
Easy! Right inside
Now it's inside
Now blow into the hat
The watch has...
vanished!
The watch will re-appear...
in someone's pocket
He has it!
Man in the red shirt!
Check your pockets
He found the watch
Come on stage, young man!
Your name?
- Deepak
I'll never smoke again.
Yesterday, my friends forced me to
I deserve at least 12,000 a month
with my qualiﬁcations
Don't negotiate.
He was my best student
Professor taught us
till 10th grade
It's thanks to him
that we are what we are
Tea, please
No thank you, I have to go...
and ﬁnish the book translation
Glass of water?
From the earthenware pot
I received your CV by e-mail
Unfortunately...
we have no positions open
for instructors
We need a receptionist
Welcoming and counseling
new students
Some database work, paid extra
Comes to 5.5K a month
Perfect!
She'll start tomorrow
Thank you so much, Sanjay!
- Oh! Come on, Sir
It's the least l could do
I must take this call
Please, have some water.
The new Earthenware pot...
makes the water taste very sweet!
He meant 5,500 rupees only
What he meant was a lot of
respect for your father
Thank you
So you're studying
at the Polytechnic Institute?
Yes. Civil engineering, ﬁnal year
We had a college strike
last year...
otherwise, I would have ajob by now
What are your hobbies?
Music
Are you a singer?
- No
I listen to music,
on radio and on CDs too
Just music?
I also like poetry a lot!
Poetry?
- Yes
Bashir Badr...
Akbar Allahabadi...
Mirza Ghalib...
You must have at least
heard of Ghalib's name?
Yeah
Here, please have some
May I get some sauce?
Schezwan sauce?
May I get some please
Please start
- No, after you
No, you go ﬁrst
So...
now we're friends right?
By the way,"-
if you're ever in trouble,
let me know
What will you do?
Ill...
sort things out for you...
if anyone bothers you...
teases you or makes you cry
There are lots of nasty boys
around here
Okay
What if...
you make me cry?
Me? No... Why?
I'd sort that out for you too
Write the student's name here,
in capital letters
This is our prospectus
with a complimentary CD
All the information is in here
Come back tomorrow and it'll be done
Thank you
- Thank you
You're quite a sweet talker!
ls this your ﬁrst job?
No
What happened to the previous job?
I didn't like the job
I know exactly where
your previous job was
Enter our "Match the Face" contest!
Guess the actors
and send us the answers
If you get it right,
you could win a brand new car!
Lines are open now...
Do you want to go in?
- Yes!
Please!
- How many coins did you ﬁnd today?
More than their fathers ever will!
Please let me compete!
Ok, relax
Let's go
Run along!
Ladies and gentlemen,
the competition has begun!
Let's see who ﬁnds the most coins
Put the coins here
Dive over there!
20 rupees on Jhonta?
How much?
Over here!
Piyush Agarwal
Hometown: Allahabad?
He passed away
Something tragic happened to him
I read about it
I'm from his coaching centre
We have some ﬁles
that belonged to him
And he owed us some money
He was to return some
books as well, so...
could I have his address please?
Come out now! The game's over
Who has the most coins?
Hey, Munna!
Who is the winner?
Jhonta!
I told you I would win
Jhoma has won 980 Rupees
You were great!
Hello?
Hide these stars safely in my eyes,
the night will be along one
Wanderers like us, will meet somewhere,
perhaps in the morning light
Then?
"And then?"
That was it
Sorry, I didn't get it. I mean
I got some of it... it was terriﬁc!
You're such a dumbo!
And very cute!
What did you just say?
I didn't say anything
But I heard that!
If I recite Chakbast, you'll faint!
Your birthday's soon, right?
I saw on Facebook
Really?
Facebook didn't tell you everything
What?
A Picnic!
Shaalu?
Mom's calling. We'll talk later
Hold on...
What is it?
Please call me by my name
Only if you memorize two poems...
then I'll decide.
I have to go now
Hello?
Bye
A poem by Dushyam Kumar
You move like the misty morning train
I tremble like a bridge in the rain
In the deep jungle of your gaze
I lose my way, no trail to blaze
Who is it?
May I speak with Ramdhari Agarwal?
Speaking. Who is this?
I... I...
What do you want? Hello?
I'm calling from Kashi
Co-operative bank
We have a new scheme
l don't need anything, thank you!
I'll come straight to the point
Will you sleep with me?
Tell me
I won't tell anyone
You had sex with him too, right?
Why are you worried about your wife?
This is good quality stuff
It's too expensive
- It is not!
Let me give you a discount
Think it over
and come back later, okay?
I quit my jqb
Pathak...
your daughter hasn't visited
for ages
Good morning
Get out of here
What?
Should I drown myself with shame?
Go away
Madam just quit her job!
What were you thinking?
Nothing
"Nothing", "l don't know",
that's all you know!
Was I ever hard on you?
I've always been liberal...
raised you like a boy
What did I do to deserve
such a scandal?
I haven't created any scandal
Then what is this?
All this scampering for loose
change! What is this?
On the ghat, in the streets...
I'm constantly afraid someone
will ask about you! What is this?
That's your fear
Hence, I've decided
not to live here anymore
The smaller the city, the
narrower the world-view
After all this, you're still living
in this house with dignity...
And my world-view is narrow?
- Wow!
How considerate of you, Father!
Should I start paying rent as well?
Look at me
What do you want from me?
Why are you taking revenge?
Revenge for what?
For Mother!
You don't even remember
what she looked like
You were just 6 years old
Are 6 year-olds blind?
I took her to the hospital, didn't l?
For 2 days, she begged you
to take her, but you didn't
Your students mattered more
You did nothing!
I thought it was just fever.
I messed up
But I never neglected you, did l?
I left my job at the university,
for your sake!
I ended up selling books
on the ghat, for your sake!
You think I killed your mother?
So do you think I killed that boy?
Answer me?
He killed himself!
You're crazy.
You're getting confused
I'm not getting confused
I will defend my honor
I won't go to prison
You have decided
everything for yourself!
I'm the fool who arranges the money
I'll arrange the ransom too
Next you'll say you don't even
need a father
Do what you feel like
I tremble like a bridge in the rain
In the deep jungle of your gaze
I lose my way, no trail to blaze
I never thought about it.
I like them all
How can you like all the seasons?
l like the monsoons!
You recorded her voice?
Brilliant!
First, I recorded it on my phone...
then I cued songs
based on her words
Well done! The student
has become the master!
That's a smart gift, bro!
Dude, she's from an upper-caste
Don't get too emotional about her
Does she know
you're from a lower caste?
Let her know about it,
then do as you please
Not everyone is progressive
Ok, I'll tell her later
Come on!
There's lot of time for that
When he gets ajob,
none of this will matter
Give him your motorbike keys
- Why?
He has one more surprise for her
Give the keys!
He'll pay you for the fuel
First word
Plant?
Lamp?
Bowl!
DeePak!
It's a ﬂower, not Deepak
Where to?
Wherever you want
Get on
Your bag?
Sorry!
Shall I sit?
- Yes, sure
You know what we
boys call your bus?
What?
Chick-Wagon!
What is this?
ls it an eraser?
-Yes
You have ﬁnal year
Civil Engineering books?
No sir
Concrete design?
- No sir
Structure analysis?
You got all your books?
Pack these please!
You never told me where you live
You know Bhelupur?
Bhelupur?
- Right after that
My friend Prerna lives there
I'll say I'm going there and
I'll visit you
Great idea, right?
You'll come to my house?
I mean... your parents won't mind?
If you don't feel like it, I won't
No, I didn't mean that
Hey, hold this for a second
This is your birthday gift
Put them on
ls it audible?
Thank you
Have you ever been to Sangam?
I come here often
In few days we'll be off on
a pilgrimage in a bus
All of us: uncle, aunt,
grandpa, and grandma
Will you come along?
\Nhere?
- With us
With yqu?
I'll have to think about it
What is it?
You must be the youngest
in your family, right?
Right! How did you know?
The youngest are always chatterboxes
That hurts! Your hand is
like a hammer!
It's the ring
My uncle gave it to me
when I was a kid
It's stuck now
My ﬁngers grew...
the ring stayed the same
Everybody loves me
because I'm the youngest
What is it?
I don't know
You're the youngest, right?
So I kissed you
Shaalu
Will you marry me?
I don't know
Will your folks agree?
You want to meet them?
Will you introduce me?
You won't tell me where you live...
but you are in a hurry to
come to my place?
Shall I go?
- You stay near by?
Around the corner,
the house on the left
Where's your house?
You said it was near Belupur...
Shivala?
Kamacha!
Ok, I got it
Durgakund, right?
- Why?
What's bothering you?
I told you I stay near Bhelupur.
You have nothing else to talk about?
I was just joking
You think this is funny?
Want to know where I live?
Come, I'll take you
Come, let me take you there and
curb your curiosity!
You want the truth?
I live by Harischchandra Ghat.
I was born and raised there
We burn bodies, light pyres
Me, my father, my uncles,
my brother... all of us, for ages
Ever see a body burn?
Tell me, have you?
I see them all day, every day.
I burn the dead, day and night
In the ﬁre, the skin melts
and all that's left is the bones
We smash the skull
and wash the ashes into the Ganges
Can you imagine?
Want to come and see?
What happened? Won't you use
your friend's pretext now?
Where's my tip?
Why?
An employment letter from the
government deserves a good tip
You're the new
employee right?
Yes
Please have a seat
Just 2 minutes later...
and you could have ﬁlled
my water bottle too
I'm Sadhya
Hello
The railway has printed a great guide
We had to learn without
books, the hard way!
Look at this...
This is Mr. Mukherjee
He used to work here
before you joined
He refused to learn computers
May I use this?
- Yes, sure
Railways relocated him to a remote
area in Rajasthan
Now he issues train tickets manually
You must be well trained
in computers?
Yes
Very nice
Ticket!
Good morning
Where to?
- Lalpur
Shaalu, aunt is calling you
You know...
you're not like the other boys!
Really? How?
There is a certain
sense of honesty in you
Like the honesty in
Nida Fazli's poetry
Now who is this Nida Fazli?
That's how honest you are!
The food was delicious...
but the salad was stale
Even the lentils were brilliant
It better be.
The owner's from our caste
So, you finally called, huh?
It was you who
overreacted that day...
and now you're mad at me?
Sum!
I didn't ask for an apology
I'm so stupid!
- That's true
I have no manners
Even that is true!
\Nhere've you reached?
Haven't even crossed the state yet
Near the border
Ok, listen...
My parents...
they...
...they'll never approve of you
They're stuck in the past
with their old-fashioned ideas
But I'm with you
With time, parents
do come around
Just get yourself a good job
Yes, I'm doing my best
Placements season is approaching.
I will do my best!
That's the spirit!
I'll handle the rest
If it comes to it,
I'll run away with you
0k, lake care! Bye!
Hey man! Let's go back!
Wejust came in!
I have a lot to study
Hey, turn the boat around
Sir... extra sheet, please
Thank you
I'm doing my ﬁnal year
in civil engineering...
from Seth Kinaram Agarwal
Polytechnique College
My career objective is to
pursue a career in engineering...
with focus on mechanical drafting
Deepak: Can't wait to see you.
I'rn about to get a job!
Shove the skull inside
I'll go get Deepak to help
Hey, Deepak
What is it?
- Hurry up
Dad's drunk again and there
are lots of bodies to burn
Wake up!
Everybody wants to avoid
work in this family!
I'm bloody tired of this
bonded labour!
Hey, Deepak!
Wait up, you thief!
One more time and I'll
throw you in these pyres!
They have not even covered
the bodies properly
Shambu!
Light some pyres there
I'm on it
Bathe this one ﬁrst
DeePak!
Light some pyres over there and
then some more over there
There?
Near the edge.
As many as you can
Shall I ﬁnish here ﬁrst?
- Yes
More sawdust!
Sikandar needs more wood.
Go help him
Deepak! Give us a hand
Be careful
Easy
Did the cops say anything?
That the pilgrims‘ bus fell
into the Ganges
Really?
Public aid workers dumped
all the bodies here
Not a single survivor?
No
You know...
28 trains stop at this station
Guess how many don't?
64!
Which means, it's
easy to come here...
but it's difﬁcult to leave!
Could you check
the status of this ticket?
Listen... l know i! was fun
But we need to get back now
One more day
Not conﬁrmed yet
Could you check the last
minute availabilities?
Even one seat for both of us is ﬁne
One seat? I like that...
No seats available
Any cancellations?
- None whatsoever!
Come and see this amazing competition!
Never before seen!
Jhonta!
And now, ladies and gentlemen...
these kids will dive
Jhonta!
He's not here. Bet on someone else
Put your money on Babua.
He's sure to win!
Put it on Babua
How much?
- 200 Rupees
Professor bets 200 on Babua!
Get ready
1...
2...
Can you see anything in my mouth?
- No!
Now I'll put this ball in my mouth.
Watch closely!
Now... 1... 2... and...
Here's your share
I deserve at least 500 Rupees
- We'll adjust it next time
How much did you lose?
Look how late it is!
Do you hear me?
Turned mute, have you?
Where were you?
Having fun
Are you hereto work or have fun?
I'm having fun with my own money!
Why is your ass on ﬁre?
Shut up!
Those other orphan kids
have ruined you
Show some respect!
You will not go anywhere
during a competition
Acting like the king of Banaras!
Throwing money down the drain!
I'll tell Devi!
Do what you want
Sit your butt here!
Don't you dare move
Sit down!
Such arrogance!
From now on,
I want all your winnings
The internship discussion topic is...
the effects of industrialization...
on human life and on society at large
Say something, Deepak
You've been quiet for
a really longtime
No, it's okay.
Take your time
"l like poetry..."
"You move like the
misty morning train...
I tremble like a bridge in the rain"
"If it comes to that,
I'll run away with you"
When does this grief ever end?
Deepak, get up!
You're being crazy!
You need to control yourself
Hey Deepak, take
my bike keys
Shaalu!!!
You promised the translation
would be done by today
The printers are sitting idle
Mr. Pathak?
ls everything 0k?
I'll deliver it within 3 days
3 more days?
Devi's not keeping
well these days
Mr. Verma...
could you give me an
advance please?
You've already kept me
hanging like a bat
Still, I can't say no
Here you go
It's ﬁne
Good bye!
Sorry for the delay!
How much is this?
30,000 Rupees for now...
Come with me
See that gate over there?
Yes
There's a shop opposite
"Pappu scrap dealer"
Sell this crappy old engine
for 10 or 15,000 Rupees
The thing is we are trying...
I think we'll be able to complete
the payment soon
You think this is a joke?
This is not enough
Are you a child?
I'll pay the rest this week
Please take this
You better clear it this week...
and complete the balance
by next month
Money?
Please hurry, sir!
Where to?
- Howrah
As a "Devi"...
you should have 4 arms on each side
8 tickets in record speed!
Sir, please hurry
What's the rush?
My father says...
if you haven't tasted kheer...
you're missing one of life's
greatest pleasures
Here, have some
No, you have it
That goes without saying
Father's cooked it himself
It's his birthday today
Oh, 0k
Wow
- Isn't it delicious?
Yes very
Do you live alone?
No, I live with my father
Father lives alone
I mean, he's alone during the day
‘Kheer’?
Haven't cooked it in
a while, so I thought...
I just had dinner. Keep it,
I'll have it tomorrow
Have it, please
You're so fond of it
It's good
ls there any milk left for
tomorrow morning?
What is it?
I completed a month
at work today. So...
it's my salary cheque
How much?
20 thousand Rupees
Great!
Come, sit next to me
You never told me your
job was conﬁrmed
It's temporary
I'll work until we arrange
the ransom money
Then...
And then?
I'm planning to take up a
course at Allahabad university
I'll work part-time
near the university
You want to move out?
Yes
Why?
If it wasn't for this case,
I would have already left
Maybe I'm better off alone
Allahabad isn't too far
I'll come back here once in a while
- What about your father?
I don't ﬁt in your life anywhere?
If you've ﬁgured out so much then...
Go
I did not kill your mother!
I'll quietly sleep on the ghat!
Father, please!
Don't cry, please
Narrow gauges are still used
in hilly areas
Broad-gauge technology
will eventually replace it
Graduated ﬁrst in your class?
- Yes
You're hired for a six-month trial
in Allahabad
Thank you, sir
- Congratulations
Now we're on it completely
Even Devi's now got a temporary job
I have a feeling we'll
pay the dues soon
6th of the next month
is your last day to pay up
Or else the video's going up
on YouTube
I'm sure you know
what YouTube is?
Dad, shall we leave?
Yes, let's go
Today on the eve of Maha Shivrazri
We will have the
biggest competition till date
So on this note
All hail in the name of...
Lord Mahadev!
All okay?
Take down my bet
- How much?
10,000 Rupees
You'll win right?
- Obviously!
Did you know Devi...
there's always one
friend in every group...
who is considered
the most wise
Yes
Back in college... I used
to be that intellectual
All my friends used to seek
my help with their problems
My advice to everyone...
whatever is in your heart,
say it out loud!
Hiding will get you nothing
Let's see who is going to win today!
Jhonta, dive there!
Hurry up! Faster!
On the extreme end
Now that you're leaving...
I think it's time I should
listen to the "intellectual" inside me...
and tell you what is in my heart
Jhonta!
Dive, Munna!
Everything okay?
Sum!
I have to leave
Give way, move!
Everybody move from here!
Give way!
Jhonta!!!
I won't ever let you play
this game, my child!
What?
I lost all your money, isn't it?
No
What happened?
Want to see a magic trick?
Do you see anything
in my hand?
Anything in this one?
No
Anything in my mouth?
1...2...3...
Whose is it?
It's for you
Where did you ﬁnd it?
Found it in the river
while diving
Yes, great!
Thank you
It's hot!
I've packed lunch.
Have it on the train
You eat, I'll pack
It's lovely
Shall we go?
Blessings
Call me once you reach
I'm off
- Hurry up
Step back
Go sit
- See you soon, Dad
Hello!
I'm hereto see Mr. Ramdhari Agarwal
I am Devi Pathak
Piyush was my friend. That day...
Hold on. It's better we talk inside!
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
- Why have you come here?
Are you okay?
Why?
What harm did he ever do to you?
Water?
30 rupees to go to Sangam!
Come on, miss!
And you, sir?
I'll take you to Sangam
ls this your ﬁrst visit to Sangam?
Yes
And you?
Second time
Someone once said you must visit
Sangam twice in a lifetime
Why?
Alone the ﬁrst time, and with
someone the second time around